I like it.
好きです
Seriously?
マジで?
Don't sleep in my house for a while.
うちにちょっと寝るな、ちょっと
Isn't the way you touch it so erotic?
触り方めっちゃエロくない?
Inside Jogi.
ジョーギーの中身
Ah, amazing.
あ、すごい
Even I have entered, now.
僕まで入っちゃった、今
Sorry.
ごめんね
Ah, amazing.
あ、すごい
So scary.
すげぇ怖い
Let's go out.
出ちゃう
Looks like it's about to come out.
出ちゃいそう
terrible.
やばい
early.
早い
It's already out.
もう出ちゃった
No, it feels a little too good.
いや、ちょっと気持ちよすぎて
Just a little more.
もうちょっと
I started.
始めました
Sorry, I hit your face.
ご めん、顔かかったね
Wasn't it amazing?
すごくなかった?
Momentum.
勢いが
amazing.
すごい
Sorry.
すいません
A lot.
いっぱいね
The blowjob feels a little too good.
ちょっとフェラーも気持ちよすぎて
Ah, it's already out.
あ、もう出ちゃったね
Sorry, just a moment.
ごめんね、ちょっと
Shall I wipe it off a bit?
ちょっと拭こうか
sorry.
ごめんなさい
I washed it a little.
ちょっと洗ってきました
Sorry.
すいません
Why did you leave?
なんでいっちゃったんですか?
It felt so good.
気持ちよすぎて
It's too early.
早すぎます
Sorry.
ごめんね
No.
だめ
It got on my face just now.
顔にかかっちゃったね、さっきね
It feels so good.
気持ちよすぎてさ
That's no good.
ダメですよ
It's too early.
早すぎる
That's amazing.
すごいね
It's delicious.
うまいね
Where did you teach?
どこで教えたの?
Did the producer tell you?
プロデューサーさんに 教えてもらったの?
what?
何?
Do you like Jinjin?
チンジン好きなの?
I like it.
好きです
That's amazing, it's me.
すごいさ、俺じゃん
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Are you leaving already?
もういっちゃうんですか?
Isn't it too early?
早すぎないですか?
I can't stand it, so just a little.
我慢できないから、ちょっと
Can I put it in?
入れてもいい?
Are you ready to put it in already?
もう入れちゃうんですか?
still?
まだ?
Is it okay to include it?
入れていいでしょ?
You want it, don't you?
欲 しいでしょ、チンジ
hmm.
ン
I want it.
欲 しいです
It's narrow, that's for sure.
狭いね、確かに
Can I have it again?
もう一回もらっていいですか?
Because she has a beautiful body.
体きれいだからね
I feel like I'm getting depressed.
うつんぱいが うつんぱいになってそう
Yeah.
うん
Amazing
すげ
ー.
ー
Erotic.
エ ロい
It's so erotic.
エロいっすね
It's tough.
きついね
Great style.
すっげースタイル
I'm laughing so hard.
すっげー笑ってる
It's soooo tight.
すっげーきつい
It's really tough.
めちゃくちゃきついね
Why is it so tight?
なんでこんなにきついの?
I don't know.
わかんない
Are you closed?
閉めてんの?
Awesome.
すっげー
My body is really weak.
体めっちゃ弱い
Did you do gymnastics?
体操やってた?
They say it's hard.
硬いって言うんだよね
It's not hard.
硬くないよ
whip?
むち?
whip.
むち
Can I take it out?
出していい?
Is it no good?
ダメなの?
why?
なんで?
Why?
どうして?
It's a whip, right?
むちでしょ?
Melting.
トロトロ
Melt it.
トロトロして
It's cute.
かわいいね
I was planning on releasing it.
出す予定だったんだけど
I've forgotten how to pronounce words.
舌目覚えやしちゃった
It's like gymnastics.
身体操みたい